const questionBank = [
    {
        question: "What is the capital city of India ?",
        option_1: "Bengaluru",
        option_2: "Kolkata",
        option_3: "New Delhi",
        option_4: "Mumbai",
        correct: "New Delhi"
    },
    {
        question: "Who came second in the FIFA Women's World Cup in 2019 ?",
        option_1: "Netherlands",
        option_2: "Australia",
        option_3: "New Zealand",
        option_4: "England",
        correct: " Netherlands"
    },
    {
        question: "What flavour chocolate would you find in a green triangle in a box of Quality Streets ?",
        option_1: "white Chocolate",
        option_2: "Dark Chocolate",
        option_3: "Praline chocolate",
        option_4: "Ruby Chocolate",
        correct: " Praline chocolate"
    },
    {
        question: "A body at rest can have?",
        option_1: "Speed",
        option_2: "Velocity",
        option_3: "Momentum",
        option_4: "Energy",
        correct: "Velocity"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following, can nither be created nor be destroyed ?",
        option_1: "Force",
        option_2: "Power",
        option_3: "Momentum",
        option_4: "Energy",
        correct: "Energy"
    },
    {
        question: "Jawaharlal Nehru port is located in ?",
        option_1: "Kerala",
        option_2: "Maharashtra",
        option_3: "Andra Pradesh",
        option_4: "West Bengal",
        correct: "Maharashtra"
    },
    {
        question: "Amaravati Stupa is located in which state of india ?",
        option_1: "Madhya Pradesh",
        option_2: "Chhattisgarh",
        option_3: "Andra Pradesh",
        option_4: "Maharashtra",
        correct: "Andra Pradesh"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is known as the 'Golden City' ?",
        option_1: "Jaisalmer",
        option_2: "Jodhpur",
        option_3: "Dungarpur",
        option_4: "Bundi",
        correct: "Jaisalmer"
    },
    {
        question: "The hill station of Chail is located in ?",
        option_1: "Himachal Pradesh",
        option_2: "Uttar Pradesh",
        option_3: "Madhya Pradesh",
        option_4: "Arunachal Pradesh",
        correct: "Himachal Pradesh"
    },
    {
        question:"Red Panda is a state animal of which of the following state ?",
        option_1: "Mizoram",
        option_2: "Manipur",
        option_3: "Meghalaya",
        option_4: "Sikkim",
        correct: "Sikkim"
    }
]